http://www.cybercoins.net/pages/privacy-statement

Large Cents
Large Cents; Flowing Hair, Liberty Cap, Draped Bust, Classic Head
World Coins French Francs
World Coins French Territories, Misc.
World Coins Great Britain Penny
World Coins Great Britain 2 Pence, 3 Pence, 4 Pence, 5 Pence
World Coins Great Britain New Pence: All denominations
World Coins Great Britain Territories, misc.
World Coins Italy Centesimo and Centesimi
World Coins Italy Lira, Lire and misc.
World Coins Netherlands 2 1/2 Cents to 50 Cents
World Coins Netherlands Guldens, misc.
US Stamps, Airmail
US Stamps: Special Delivery, Postage Due, Official, Revenues, etc.
Large Cents
Large Cents; Flowing Hair, Liberty Cap, Draped Bust, Classic Head
World Coins French Francs
World Coins French Territories, Misc.
World Coins Great Britain Penny
World Coins Great Britain 2 Pence, 3 Pence, 4 Pence, 5 Pence
World Coins Great Britain New Pence: All denominations
World Coins Great Britain Territories, misc.
World Coins Italy Centesimo and Centesimi
World Coins Italy Lira, Lire and misc.
World Coins Netherlands 2 1/2 Cents to 50 Cents
World Coins Netherlands Guldens, misc.
US Stamps, Airmail
US Stamps: Special Delivery, Postage Due, Official, Revenues, etc.
Privacy statement
Cybercoins.net (CNI) will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any customer identifiable information derived from the use of CNI -- including user names and addresses -- without the consent of the user (except as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the customer or others). When CNI uses other agents, contractors or companies to drop ship out of stock items, CNI may disclose user identifiable information to such parties, but will use reasonable efforts to ensure that such parties protect your personally identifiable information consistent with this Privacy Statement.
To help make the CNI Site more responsive to demands of its users, CNI may invoke a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie." A cookie is a small, encrypted data string which our server writes to your hard drive which contains your unique user ID for our site. We use cookies to deliver web content specific to your interests, to keep track of your order as you order services, and to control access to our content. A cookie is not used to access or otherwise compromise the data on your hard drive. You can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies if you do not want us to establish and maintain a unique CNI user ID. Please be aware that cookies may be required to complete certain functions on the CNI Site, such as ordering.
CNI's owned or leased web servers supporting the CNI Site may automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data --such as the web pages you view.) CNI uses this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor the CNI Site to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our site.
To make the CNI Site more valuable to its users, we may offer some features in conjunction with other providers. Our site may also include links to other web sites whose privacy practices and policies we do not control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the address --known as a URL-- in the location bar on your browser), use of any information that you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site that you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you cannot find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.
All information gathered on this site is stored within Cybercoins.net-owned or -leased databases which are intended to be accessed only by Cybercoins.net Inc., Shopify.com, and/or its agents. However, as effective as any security measure implemented by Cybercoins.net may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of such databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
Please note that this Privacy Statement applies only to the collection, use, and disclosure of information and/or other data derived from the use of the CNI Site, and does not apply to the collection, use, or disclosure of any information and/or other data derived other than from the use of the CNI Site. In addition, please note that this Privacy Statement does not apply to any CNI customer contracts, notwithstanding that the terms and conditions of such contracts may be available to CNI customers on the CNI Site.
A final note: the Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change this Privacy Statement at some point in the future, we'll post the changes to the CNI Site. Please check back regularly.
For questions regarding the above statement, contact: Cybercoins.net Inc., 2925 West Liberty Ave., Pittsburgh, PA 15216, USA.
